Summer vacations are about to begin, and you might be planning a trip
with your kids and family.
If you want your
holiday trip to be stress-free, consider taking travel
insurance. Travel insurance not
only protects
you and your family from any travel emergencies, but also
insures your luggage, passport, credit cards, ATMs, etc.
In this video, let's explore why travel insurance is necessary
and its benefits.
Travel insurance
is a type of insurance that provides security in the event of medical expenses,
strip cancellation, mishaps, flight cancellations, and
other losses.
Therefore, travel insurance is a better option for protecting you from
all the problems that may arise during travel.
If a flight is delayed or canceled,
travel insurance covers the
expenses incurred due to this, such as food, drinks, hotel accommodation, and other expenses.
If your luggage is lost or
stolen during travel, travel insurance covers
it.
If a person loses his or her life during travel or meets with an
accident,  Then the hospital
expenses are also included in the travel insurance tax. The
insurance company offers policies of fixed amount according to the duration of the trip,
number of members coming in the trip and destination.
Generally, the company offers coverage ranging
from 15000 to 5 million dollars for foreign trips.
After taking the policy,
it can be cancelled before going on the trip.
If you liked this video,
if you are also planning to travel,
then definitely watch our video, who knows what can happen
when.
If you liked our video, then do
not forget to like and share it and subscribe to the channel Na Bhole
[Prashasa]